Ryan Stewart: What's up, everybody?
Ryan Stewart: How we doing, how we doing?
Ryan Stewart: How can I change my video settings? It looks like I got makeup on, right?
Ryan Stewart: What kind of settings do I have on here?
Ryan Stewart: No, that's a little bit better.
Ryan Stewart: Hey, Jason, how we doing, man?
Ryan Stewart: How's everyone doing?
Ryan Stewart: Get myself set up here.
Ryan Stewart: See if David's here… Alright, get David up here. Yo, what's up, Austin? Mike?
Ryan Stewart: I'm excited too, Jason. I'm very excited. Got a lot of good stuff. It's a nice day for a Zoom.
Ryan Stewart: Always a nice day for a Zoom.
Ryan Stewart: Sunny evening in the Ute, tempted to get a beer. Go ahead, David, enjoy yourself, why not? YOLO, right?
Ryan Stewart: We're gonna be doing some… Some fun stuff. I mean, some fun stuff for us nerds anyways, right?
Ryan Stewart: My wife doesn't think it's fun, but…
Ryan Stewart: I enjoy it. I enjoy what I do. What's up, Ryan?
Ryan Stewart: Let some more people trickle in.
Ryan Stewart: Let me see if David's… oh, what's up, David? There you go. Kremit.
Ryan Stewart: Alright…
Ryan Stewart: Oh, that's why my speakers weren't working.
Ryan Stewart: What's up, Connor?
Ryan Stewart: What's everyone working on?
Ryan Stewart: Anyone got some big leads in the pipeline that they're excited to get some proposals out to?
Ryan Stewart: Talk to me.
Ryan Stewart: Got a few more minutes here. It's only 2.02.
Ryan Stewart: Gonna give people a few more minutes. I live in Miami. We operate on something here called Miami Time.
Ryan Stewart: Which means everyone's at least 20 to 30 minutes late. Actually, restaurants, interestingly enough, have a built-in 15-minute grace period. I'm sure they do in other cities, but, like, in Miami, it's like,
Ryan Stewart: On reservations, it's like a standard thing, like, you're not hitting the reservation on time.
Ryan Stewart: New campfire.
David Krevitt: stay in Miami.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, dude, it's a fucking joke.
Ryan Stewart: Mike, you got a new campaign starting, that's awesome.
Ryan Stewart: VSL funnel, what do you got going on?
Ryan Stewart: Adrian said, building on reporting tool on Claude, I think I'm addicted. Yeah, that's been known to happen.
Ryan Stewart: Claude has been known to… I'm actually in a bit of a burnout stage right now, if I'm being completely honest, because I went through, like, a month period where it was like…
Ryan Stewart: I was only talking to Claude, and just only doing stuff through Claude.
Ryan Stewart: if I'm being honest, when David built this, I had to sit down and go through it. I had to, like, put on…
Ryan Stewart: the deepest thinking hat that I possibly could, because it definitely… it's like a mental exhaustion thing. So enjoy the addiction while you can, because it does tend to…
Ryan Stewart: it… it's… it… it's… it can be… it can be mentally exhausting. Brain fatigue, as Krista said, yeah.
David Krevitt: Yeah, you gotta take breaks. Yeah.
David Krevitt: That's what clients are for, you know?
Ryan Stewart: So that's what clients are for?
David Krevitt: Yeah, just meetings, meet people.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, my clients aren't the most… aren't the most fun folks.
Ryan Stewart: I'm actually building a website. I told Cesar we're never doing a website again, because we have a new client we're doing a website for, and they're attorneys, so they just, like, man, I love them, they're great people.
Ryan Stewart: But nitpicking, I mean, they went to…
David Krevitt: Very detailed.
Ryan Stewart: Oh, dude, they were like… we don't, like, double space at the beginning of paragraphs. I was like… What?
Ryan Stewart: Like, what does that even mean? They're like, there's two spaces at the beginning of every sentence. We like single. And I was like…
Ryan Stewart: No, I can't do this problem.
David Krevitt: Yeah, duly noted, but…
Ryan Stewart: I'm not going through an entire website and changing that, that's not happening.
Ryan Stewart: They're extremely detail-oriented.
Ryan Stewart: Mike says, like and hate Claude, great output, terrible allowances, may have to upgrade. Definitely upgrade, man. I tell people all the time, like.
Ryan Stewart: just pay… pay the most that you can for it. It's worth it. Especially going through this program, you're probably gonna need it. And it… once you get, like, the workflows down, it becomes a lot easier.
Ryan Stewart: Adam said as Claude Opus got worse, we built a full internal agency dashboard across a number of months.
Ryan Stewart: So feel the exhaustion from the comments. I don't know if it's gotten worse, but, you know, like, we're gonna talk about things in this. Like I said, I'm very honest and transparent about it. I don't own Claude, so, like, I have no problem, like, attacking it or talking shit about it when it's not performing, but, like, it does hiccup, you know? It will definitely…
Ryan Stewart: give you different outputs. But it's important to focus on the outcome.
Ryan Stewart: And the fact that you're still saving a tremendous amount of time on what we're doing, you just have to spend a little bit more time, you know, proofreading stuff and going through it.
Ryan Stewart: And when you have a team structure like I do, I'm working with somebody who's doing it, and then I'm reviewing. We kind of have that same doer and reviewer structure that's been the blueprint for, like, 15 years now. It works very well, because I'll catch stuff that Annette, who is my, you know, sales person, doesn't catch, and I just re-prompt it off the HTML, and it's golden. So, with that being said.
Ryan Stewart: Let's go ahead and get started with the presentation. Let me just get set up here.
Ryan Stewart: Slideshow this guy.
Ryan Stewart: Alright.
Ryan Stewart: So, we are going to be covering the SEO Proposal Agent.
Ryan Stewart: you know, this could be… this could be used for a general search. I kind of… this is kind of like our SEO in general. There's GEO that's also included in this. It's becoming a very core staple part of our SEO pitches, so that's included in this as well. You can very easily fold paid search into here, and as we grow and expand this program, these modules, we'll include that in here as well.
Ryan Stewart: But, you know, an important thing about this program and what we're teaching is really trying to impart you on, giving you a foundational.
Ryan Stewart: foundational file that can get you started, get you, like, 80% of the way there, maybe 70% of the way there, and then you put in a little bit of extra time to get it customized, get it tailored to exactly what you need. But I'm excited because
Ryan Stewart: We've been using…
Ryan Stewart: a version of this for our proposals at our agency right now. We've had a very good streak the past two months of SEO opportunities. Geo's really been picking up in the legal space.
Ryan Stewart: And, we've been closing…
Ryan Stewart: We closed 3 deals using this proposal, it's 3 for 3. I don't want to say it was just the proposal, but we're definitely getting a lot of really good feedback from it, and I believe it's because we're able to hyper-focus on elements of the proposal that actually stand out to the prospect, instead of just a template that takes 8 hours to put together. So…
Ryan Stewart: What we're going to talk about today, number one, I'm gonna start with just what are the foundations of a proposal? What should be in a proposal? What do you need to cover? And whenever you're doing anything inside of Claude, I know I was on an Inner Circle call just yesterday, talking to somebody who was working on
Ryan Stewart: an analysis report, an SEO analysis report, and I was like, look, you need to start with the foundations of, like, what are the bullet points that you're just trying to get from this?
Ryan Stewart: like, just start there. So it's important that we start with those things before we get into the details of the proposal, because this thing is… it's big. There's a lot of stuff in here, and you know, it's important to understand these things, because as you're going through and iterating on this and customizing it, you always want to come back to these core foundational things and be like, look.
Ryan Stewart: we can get very overwhelming here with information. Extremely overwhelming with information.
Ryan Stewart: what we want to try and do is strip down. Cloud can get very wordy, it can throw a lot of information in here. You gotta put yourself in the shoes of your prospect. I work with lawyers, like.
Ryan Stewart: This stuff, if you send them a proposal like this with 40 pages, and you're like, oh, this is awesome, they're gonna be like.
Ryan Stewart: Right over my head, right? So, we're gonna talk about
Ryan Stewart: setting up a proposal, what you need for it, and then, ultimately, a lot of time on customizing it to get it to look and feel, and speak to your agency's needs. Sound good?
Ryan Stewart: So, let's jump in with the foundation. So, there's really 3
Ryan Stewart: core things that I believe every proposal should have. Number one is going to be a clear demonstration
Ryan Stewart: Of your understanding of the problem.
Ryan Stewart: So, first and foremost, that's gonna come from your discovery, right? So the discovery call that you have with a prospect, you should never, ever, ever send a proposal without having at least one call with a prospect.
Ryan Stewart: Reason being is, one, you want to be able to gather the information in terms of what it is specifically that they're looking for, but two, because
Ryan Stewart: it takes a lot of work, and if you don't have a conversation to build some FaceTime with a prospect, they're probably just gonna…
Ryan Stewart: ignore it, especially with a proposal of these sizes. So what I like to do is I'll just do it over Zoom, I'll record it, Zoom takes a transcription of it, and I'll actually feed it
Ryan Stewart: into Claude when I'm building this to give context for the conversation of what I have, or I'll just take the notes from that call and feed it into Claude, because we'll start talking about angles in a second, and that's really where Claude separates itself from
Ryan Stewart: the other stuff. So, the other part of the demonstration of the problem is going to be a deep analysis of the problem. So, looking at
Ryan Stewart: performance, gaps in performance, past marketing efforts, competitors. If you've been in the Blueprint program for a while and gone through our sales module, I've been talking about the top 10 analysis for the longest period of time. It's essentially going through and saying, these are the top 10 issues
Ryan Stewart: and opportunities that we found when auditing your website. That's very important, because selling marketing services is a consultation, it's not a Wolf Wall Street hard close. We want to show them, through our analysis, that we understand the problem, and that we're capable of tackling and solving that problem with the scope of work.
Ryan Stewart: That we're gonna pitch, but a lot of proposals that I audit from agencies are just the scope of work. It's like, here's a proposal for what we can do for you, but they skip over the, here's what's going on with your website, why it hasn't worked. And when you do… when you add in that element of customization on the front end.
Ryan Stewart: You build a lot more trust in terms of your…
Ryan Stewart: understand their understanding of your ability to solve the problem, but also it's just good information for them. Everyone loves hearing about their business. Everyone loves hearing about the competitors and what they're doing. So, this proposal is really rooted in that. I would say 80% of this proposal is analysis.
Ryan Stewart: And then after that, it gets into the scope of work, which is just templated, and you can, you know, customize it, change it as needed, but for the most part, our SEO scopes are the exact same. We're just changing, maybe, the amount of content, the amount of links we're building, and the pricing, and that can be easily prompted inside of this as well.
Ryan Stewart: So you just want to make sure that in the scope of work, the proposed solutions, you're going over, proposed services, basically what they're getting, the deliverables, the timeline, and then the pricing and the cost. And the final piece to me is just.
Ryan Stewart: have you done this before, and can you prove it, and what can I expect from this, right? So, problem, proposed scope of work, what can I expect as a result of this scope of work? So we'll do, trajectory analysis, just in terms of
Ryan Stewart: ROI analysis, very high-level stuff, we'll walk you through all this stuff. And then also examples of similar campaigns, so we put in screenshots from our Ahrefs, that I'll show you. I'm gonna show you our agency's actual proposal, a side-by-side with a template that we built for you, and just talk you through how we
Ryan Stewart: customize the base template that you get access to to what you see inside of our agency's proposals. And the final piece here, and this to me is the most important part.
Ryan Stewart: is… this has all been done in our previous proposals before. You guys all have access to our proposal templates. I've been building proposal templates for 15 years and giving them away to the program here, and they're awesome. They're really, really good. But the problem with them is that while we go through and we do, like, a custom analysis, it's still within the framework of a very rigid template, because
Ryan Stewart: I had to hire somebody full-time, her name's Annette, who only helps me with proposals, just, like, on the sales analysis side, because
Ryan Stewart: it can take upwards of 6 to 8 hours to put together a template inside of a slide deck, and it's all inside of the Blueprint Training Sales Module. You can see all that if you haven't seen it yet. But it's a very big, templated document, it's awesome, it's in Google Slides, but just putting that together took a ton of her time, and she wasn't able to put in
Ryan Stewart: too much custom analysis. The analysis that we did was in the scope of a framework, if that makes sense, right? Like, traffic analysis, competitor analysis, right? And, like.
Ryan Stewart: But what really sells is when you're able to drill into angles. An angle is almost like a story that you're telling the prospect. So, this is where AI
Ryan Stewart: really helps you separate your proposals, and what I'm really seeing from the success of ours is my ability to leverage
Ryan Stewart: AI to build these proposals, saving that a ton of time, and then also use AI to say, okay, here's an example of an angle. Easy one. Traffic is falling, right? That gives us an angle to sell
Ryan Stewart: our service based on the fact that they're losing traffic, right? The one that I'm gonna show you, actually, they're ranking first in the Maps Pack. We usually, like, lead with Maps Pack stuff, because it's a lot more impactful from a phone call point of view, but they're leading with Maps Pack, but their website traffic's falling, and they're not being found in GEO. So the point is that we're able to push these little levers, or angles, if you will.
Ryan Stewart: to be able to actually sell what we're doing. Another good example is, like, okay, what if their traffic's going up, and they're ranking first? They have 4 locations, and they're ranking first. What are we gonna sell someone that's already winning? Well, an angle that we can propose is trying to help them open up new office locations, right?
Ryan Stewart: So, little things like that, those are angles, because I have heard it all the time from prospects. They're like, Ryan, this proposal that you sent us, the previous one, this is great, but, like, we've seen this before. Like, we get audited all the time from people, and they tell us that we're doing shit work, like, we get it, blah blah blah, but, like.
Ryan Stewart: what else? You know what I mean? Like, we know this, right? Like, we can go into Ahrefs, too, and put this in. So, this is where it's so impactful, and what I really love about what David built here, when we look at the Claude thing, is it goes through and it presents angles to you to review and approve.
Ryan Stewart: So you don't have to figure out the story. Claude is actually doing that for you, because we basically built and trained it on it. So, it's really, really awesome stuff. Then we'll just jump in a second. So those are the foundations, right? These are things that we always want to come back to when you're going through and editing yours. If you're getting… you find yourself getting off the rails with your proposal, it's very easy to happen. Come back to this. Do I understand the problem?
Ryan Stewart: Am I demonstrating our expertise and experience? Do I have a clearly defined scope of work, expected results, and do I have an angle, right? And I'll show you those angles, in a second as we get in.
David Krevitt: Pierre had a good question here.
Ryan Stewart: Fire away.
David Krevitt: if Discovery Call doesn't identify a clear and immediate problem, or a clear and immediate need for services, like, how do you… how do you deal with that?
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, that's gonna come onto you. So, I actually… it's a great point, I didn't cover this. Experience, right? So…
Ryan Stewart: gain from discovery, because a lot of times you're right here, if you're talking to an HVAC contractor, he's like, dude, I don't know. Like, I don't… I don't even know how to log into my website. What are we talking about here? You know, I just want… I just want signed clients, I don't even care about my phone ringing.
Ryan Stewart: That's going to be up to you to leverage your experience, your subject matter expertise to tell them a story, right? And that's something that you want to consider, too.
Ryan Stewart: When you're going through that, if you're talking to somebody who… is…
Ryan Stewart: completely obliv… they're qualified… I'll say they're qualified, because a lot of times when somebody's completely oblivious, they're probably not qualified, but if they are qualified, just in terms of, like, hey, they have a business.
Ryan Stewart: They're doing revenue, they're doing good, they just need help in this area.
Ryan Stewart: that's going to be up to you to find that angle and tell that angle. And again, a lot of those are just rooted based on your experience. So, you just want to make sure that you are relating it to the prospect in a manner that they can understand. We don't want to try and… we don't want to talk over somebody's head or, you know, talk around them.
Ryan Stewart: So, good question, Pierre, because I agree, a lot of the times a discovery call doesn't come up with that.
Ryan Stewart: But just an example for me, because I talk to lawyers all the time, who don't necessarily know the marketing angle of it, but they know the general
Ryan Stewart: They know the general problem, which is usually, yeah, we've been paying somebody
Ryan Stewart: 10 grand a month for 2 years, and, like, we don't even know what we're getting, right? Like, we're unsure of what we're getting, so a lack of clarity. I would want to really leverage, like, data analysis reporting, and I will make sure to build in something inside of here that's going to show them a report that we do. I've been showing people live how we're using Claude to do reporting, too, which is kind of cool.
Ryan Stewart: So there's that element of it, to be like, yo, you get full transparency, you always see what we're doing, what we're building. That's one that I hear a lot. Another one is just…
Ryan Stewart: we're not getting any signed cases, right? Like, why aren't we getting signed cases? So, when I hear that, I say, okay, let's look at the specific keywords that they're ranking for, and I'll show you in some of these analysis. Maybe they're getting… they'll do, like… our traffic is going up according to our SEO agency, but we're not getting any signed clients for it. Why?
Ryan Stewart: We don't know. Maybe SEO's just not working. They say, oh, we're getting more traffic, but like, I don't know, I don't check the traffic, how do I really know that? Well, we can look at the keywords that they're ranking for. Are they just…
Ryan Stewart: growing organic traffic based on a ton of top funnel blog content. They're not going after those bottom funnel keywords. We'll cover that in the proposal element that I show you here, Pierre, but it's a very good question. A lot of times, they're not going to tell you. They're not gonna be like, this is what our problem is, but
Ryan Stewart: there's some words that you can pick up on in there, just in terms of, like, their pain points. Like, are you… this goes into the discovery questions, which we have a really good template for, like, are you currently with an agency?
Ryan Stewart: okay, what's the story with the contract? Are you guys locked in? Tell me about…
Ryan Stewart: Why are we talking? Is there something that they could have done better? Is there something that they missed? You just want to try and drag that out of them, to try and get there.
Ryan Stewart: Alright, so proposal setup. David, do you want to take over here and just kind of talk through this?
Ryan Stewart: We have a video inside of school, too. Elena, you can link to it that shows this step-by-step over the shoulder.
Ryan Stewart: I don't know if you want to share your screen, David, I can show mine, too. Share mine and Claude, or if you just want to talk high level here.
David Krevitt: Yeah, we can talk high level. Basically, there's a zip folder that's in school, that you all have access to, and that zip folder, when you download it and unzip it, it contains both an MCP server.
David Krevitt: Yeah, if you want to pull up the school module, it contains…
David Krevitt: an MCP server, which is an MCPB file, which you can basically upload to Cloud Desktop, use it with desktop or co-work. You can also open Cloud Code.
David Krevitt: In the… in the file that… in the folder that you downloaded it in. And then it also includes skill files. Each skill file is a zip.
David Krevitt: So the proposal generator is one ZIP skill file, and you just upload all of those, into Cloud Desktop to use them in desktop or co-work. So, it's basically…
David Krevitt: Yeah, that's all… that's all in school in, like, a detailed video that walks you through it.
Ryan Stewart: This video right here, David, gives just step-by-step. I actually went through it this morning when I was reinstalling it, so,
Ryan Stewart: just watch this step by step. And also, too, David, right? Because we… we are going to be updating this over time, probably, right? Like, let's say, for example, we get feedback from you guys, you're like, hey, this… we want to see this, we added in.
Ryan Stewart: they have to reinstall… when we push an update, they have to come back here and re-download it, correct? To push it back in, right?
David Krevitt: Yep, yep, exactly.
Ryan Stewart: Okay, so just something, if you're watching this, and we're pushing updates, we will continuously update this file here over time. We'll make announcements inside of school, inside of Slack, via email, and to push updated versions, just like software, you just come up here, reinstall it, just watch this video, and just go through it again. And if you have any questions with this.
Ryan Stewart: As always, ask us in Slack.
Ryan Stewart: You can send us an email, and… we will…
Ryan Stewart: Do our best to help you troubleshoot this stuff.
Ryan Stewart: It can be a little bit confusing at first, guys, I'll be the first to tell you that. I ping David sometimes for help, but once you go through this once or twice, it becomes a bit of second nature, and I've talked about this before.
Ryan Stewart: It's worth the time to figure this stuff out, because… These are the workflows.
Ryan Stewart: Of the future, if you will. We're gonna talk about the tools right now, David. Anything else in the setup, David, that you want to talk about, or we'll just…
David Krevitt: I think the one… one key way of working thing that we've talked… we've gone through a bit, Ryan, is, like, you're working in a root folder, right? So you create a folder for your agency, right? And all of your leads and clients and all of the content will, you know, be…
David Krevitt: be written by the MCP server and by Cloud, like, into that specific folder. And that's also… you can use that folder to set up, like, a project in Cloud Desktop or Cloud Co-work.
David Krevitt: But it's important to, like, have that folder… have some way of sharing that folder amongst your team, right? So you could use GitHub to share that folder, if you use the Google Drive desktop app, you can share that folder, or Dropbox, or whatever it is.
David Krevitt: But you will want, amongst your team, like, some way of sharing, kind of syncing those files in that folder, across everyone that you work with.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so Jeff just asked, David, Jeff, we just pushed it live this morning, so you'll need to reinstall the BPT OS.
Ryan Stewart: should take 5 minutes to do it, and then you'll have access to all the new skills, all the updated stuff. So, as Dave was referring to… go ahead, Dan.
David Krevitt: Yeah, John, to your question on multiple clients within this, it's basically a folder within your root folder for your agency. Ryan has it up on screen now.
David Krevitt: It's like…
Ryan Stewart: here.
David Krevitt: Clients, so each client will have a sub… its own subfolder, and same with, you know, every lead that you're making proposals.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so in this case, this is for, proposals, so it's a lead, right? So the one that I'm gonna walk you through is Jeffco Criminal Defense. The proposal, all the stuff, the proposal stuff is in here, so the inputs that I'm gonna show you right now in a second, the screenshots, the,
Ryan Stewart: CSV files that we need to build this. I'm gonna walk you through that in just one second. They're all inside of here, as you can see, right? So, I keep this on my desktop, and then Annette and I are working now on pushing this stuff up to GitHub so we can share this stuff together and just kind of, like, push and refresh.
Ryan Stewart: Also, too, Annette and I will… I don't want… we'll talk about this later, but Annette and I will also share HTML files of… she'll run it and send me the HTML file, and you can… I can also edit it that way.
Ryan Stewart: if I just want to edit that single proposal template, which we'll talk about when we get into more of the customization stuff.
Ryan Stewart: But, again, this is where I store this stuff, and we're gonna go through this stuff in just one second. Having one folder for everything, does that confuse context?
David Krevitt: Yeah, so Claude, like, Co-Work and Cloud Code are… they're pretty good at navigating folder structures, so…
David Krevitt: yeah, if you have a folder per client, like, it's gonna navigate it and only pull in files that it needs for whatever you're doing. You can certainly, if you want to create, like, a
David Krevitt: desk… called desktop or co-work project, like, per client, you can absolutely do that and just select the client folder, as the active folder, but yeah, the MCP server will know where to find stuff.
Ryan Stewart: It will also do it for you, David. Yeah, sorry. So, like, when I set this up today, and I was running it for the first time, I gave it the name of the firm, and it created this folder for me with all these folders inside of it. So, the MCP file that David built for you.
Ryan Stewart: when you install it, and you say… and I'm gonna walk you through this in a second, guys, so…
Ryan Stewart: We can save a lot of these questions as they come up.
Ryan Stewart: And maybe I'll wait till the end of this, too, so we can have a cleaner Q&A here, but Claude is gonna do a lot of this for you. David built this around that, so we can do that for you. I'm gonna save some of these questions. Keep firing them away, guys, but I'm gonna save some of them to the end, just so we can get through this, so… but, like, ask them as you come up here, so that way, just in terms of the recording this, we just have a cleaner transcript. So,
Ryan Stewart: Yes, somebody does ask if we need Windsor plus
Ryan Stewart: We don't actually use Windsor for this, I believe, David, for the proposal. We do use manual exports.
David Krevitt: Not for this, yeah.
Ryan Stewart: It's… it's much cleaner, to be honest with you guys. Like, Windsor can be a bit of a pain sometimes, in terms of the data pull, so…
Ryan Stewart: it's easier… it's a bit of work to get all this data, I'm gonna walk you through this now, but, like, this is what it takes to build this proposal, and some of you might not be doing local SEO, so you might not need local Falcon. Some of you might not have Screaming Frog, or…
Ryan Stewart: there's one slide in here on Tactical SEO. You don't have to put it in, and we'll talk about that in the customization of it. So, we built kind of a foundation here that has
Ryan Stewart: a wide…
Ryan Stewart: range of stuff, but you can chop it down, or even add to it very easily. So, a lot of this is just driven off of Ahrefs, the manual exports of traffic data, and it will walk you through this, you don't have to take notes on this. When you actually set it up.
Ryan Stewart: Claude will tell you everything that it needs.
Ryan Stewart: Verbatim.
Ryan Stewart: to build the proposal, which I'll walk you through in a second. So it's gonna need the traffic export data from Ahrefs, top pages, and screenshots, too, for the reporting, and I'll show you that in a second. Referring domains export for the backlinks portion of this, Screaming Frog.
Ryan Stewart: Website crawl, local Falican, if it's local, for every location that they have, a 5x5 ranking grid, the data points, scan, and I'll show you how to pull that in a second. And then also manual screenshots as well, just to kind of round out the visuals of the proposal.
Ryan Stewart: What I find with Claude, I was talking about this on his Inner Circle call yesterday.
Ryan Stewart: if you don't add in a little bit of your own flair to it, you can kind of tell that it was built and clawed. I don't mean that as a good thing, like.
Ryan Stewart: because I think in a year or two from now, as more people start adopting this, and they don't go through the level of detail that we're pushing you all to do now.
Ryan Stewart: it's gonna become very redundant, it's gonna become very commoditized. And people are gonna look at a proposal and be like, yeah, I'm just gonna… I have media blindness to us because of the fonts, the cut, like, everything was just, like, a clot output, right?
Ryan Stewart: So, I like to put screenshots in there, because to me, it makes it much easier to look at, much easier to digest, and I'll show you our agency proposal, so that will make sense as well.
Ryan Stewart: And then proposal customization, so…
Ryan Stewart: a big note here, just again, as anything with Claude, your first run is never gonna be your last. Alright? Like, there's gonna be elements of…
Ryan Stewart: double-checking that you need to do, you need to double-check the data against Ahrefs sometimes, just pop open Ahrefs, just kind of scan through it, just make sure that everything looks copothetic. Check the layout, sizing, fonts. Keep in mind, we're building you guys a template.
Ryan Stewart: based off, really, what we do at our agency, but we're all snowflakes here, right? We're all different and unique. You guys have your own…
Ryan Stewart: client base, you have your own service that you're running, maybe you're not doing local SEO, maybe you're doing single location local SEO. This one is built for multiple location SEO, because that's what we do. So, some of the layouts might get a little bit wonky, just because when you're translating your data into it, so just…
Ryan Stewart: Don't freak out, just prompt it. Claude is very good when you just go through it and just build… I build, like, a mega prompt that I'll go through. I actually sent it to David last night, where I'll go through and just, slide by slide, just take notes on the things that I want to see changed. You just re-prompt it, and it will take care of it. And that's important here, too, like…
Ryan Stewart: We, internally at our agency, used this proposal template to get started with, But now, we use…
Ryan Stewart: an element of the HTML output of the final version that we'll just re-prompt over and over again. We don't actually run this proposal generation all the time, and that's important because,
Ryan Stewart: you know, that's kind of how you keep your brand feel and your look, and again, I'm gonna show you side-by-side two of them, and you're gonna see our Weber's proposal, and it…
Ryan Stewart: it looks different. Visually, it's the same data, but it looks different, right? Because there's a certain look and feel. We fed our brand guidelines, I have a link here that I'm gonna show you in a second.
Ryan Stewart: And also just, again, like, the styling, the formatting, we will… whenever we launch a new proposal, we'll just upload a… the HTML output of a previous one that we like, and we'll start there, and then build off of that, because it has all that stuff there. I don't know if you have anything to add on this, David.
David Krevitt: Yeah, ultimately it's just web pages, right? So all this, you know, there's a lot of data analysis involved with this proposal agent, but it has about 20
David Krevitt: template HTML pages, and so those are your, you know, you have those, or will have those, like, when you download them. They're yours to modify, right? You can add new ones, you can modify the existing ones, and Claude is really good, as we know, at modifying web pages, basically.
Ryan Stewart: Alright, so once you have the MCP installed, you just go to Cowork, and I just prompted, and I said.
Ryan Stewart: zoom up here. I said, let's run a new proposal for Jeffco Criminal Defense Lawyers. Here's the website using the BPT proposal agent, right? So, some prompt along that. Had to do a little setup thing here. You might have to go through that too, but you should be fine.
Ryan Stewart: It goes through, it gives me the firm summary here, just kind of, like, some high-level information from what it crawled, just to make sure that we have the right business that we're talking about here. And then it goes through and asks me some… a little bit more details about the lead itself, who's the point of contact.
Ryan Stewart: How did it come in? I actually asked this to research and suggest competitors. You can do that, or you can provide your own. I asked it to research to see what to come up with.
Ryan Stewart: But we also kind of did our own competitive analysis. I'm going to show you all the data that we fed it here as well. And then, I just confirmed the locations that it had for it as well.
Ryan Stewart: So these are the competitors that it came up with, right? It just crawled…
Ryan Stewart: found four competitors based on search overlap, asked me if I want to use those, and then what's the expected deal value for this lead? I put it at $10,000 a month, that's usually, like, our kind of average SEO deal right now. So now, this is what I was talking about, like, it will prompt you on everything that you need to
Ryan Stewart: feed it in order to build the full proposal, right? So, Ahrefs traffic history, Ahrefs Top Pages CSV. You literally just go into Ahrefs, right, and just…
Ryan Stewart: Pull the data.
Ryan Stewart: you guys should know how to do this, I'm just gonna give you kind of, like, high level here as well, right? So if we did, like, Jeffcoat…
Ryan Stewart: Jeffco, let me get the domain, sorry, y'all.
Ryan Stewart: So, it says that it needs traffic history, Ahrefs, top pages, CSV. So, if we come down to Top Pages…
Ryan Stewart: And then, let me get our heads out of here… export, right? So now I've got the export here.
Ryan Stewart: And it will also tell me where it needs to go, right? So, in the inputs folder, right? So I'm gonna pop back open the folder that we have here.
Ryan Stewart: So…
Ryan Stewart: this is our agency OS, right? This is the folder that's connected to it. It's gonna go inside of Leads.
Ryan Stewart: Inside of the one that it created for it, Proposals.
Ryan Stewart: and then the inputs here, right? So you can see inputs, and then it has all these folders here, and then you can see what I've done already.
Ryan Stewart: is, you know, it takes 20-30 minutes to pull all this data. There's quite a bit of stuff that it needs here, I'm not gonna lie, like, it does take 20-30 minutes to put all this stuff in here. But trust me when I tell you, it's much faster than building this by hand the way that we used to with, like.
Ryan Stewart: Exporting it, pivot tables, formatting, copy and past, like.
Ryan Stewart: Trust me, this is gonna save you a lot of time. But it does require a lot of data if you want to get this level of analysis. So all the folders are mapped here, right? Ahrefs, Local Falcon, Screaming Frog, it will walk you through, again, step-by-step, everything that you need. Local Falcon is a, is a pretty important one here.
Ryan Stewart: So when you run the scan reports, you can just download this data here, and you can download it as scan report, data points, CSV, just download both of these. And we will also take…
Ryan Stewart: A actual screenshot of the ranking as well.
Ryan Stewart: And we'll add it.
Ryan Stewart: We'll add it into the screenshots folder here as well. I don't know why it didn't pop in there. I put it in the local Falcon one.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so there's screenshots in here as well, of the local Falcon that we'll put in here.
Ryan Stewart: Because we'll pull those, as I said, into the proposal. So…
Ryan Stewart: There's some questions I'm already seeing coming in about Search Atlas, and other tools. David, how… if somebody wanted to use a different tool here…
Ryan Stewart: Is it open to that? How does that… how does that work?
David Krevitt: Definitely. So, well, first thing is, within the zip file.
David Krevitt: it includes, like, the completed MCP server and the completed skills, but also all of the underlying code.
David Krevitt: Right? That's feeding the MCP server. So you, if you're comfortable going into Cloud Code and opening that folder, then you can ask it to say, hey, I want to use Search Atlas.
David Krevitt: Here, or there was a couple other tools mentioned, for the proposal. And it will help you do that.
David Krevitt: Definitely, if you want help setting that up, like, just ping us in support.
David Krevitt: And we can… can see if we can help you do that. But it… the whole thing is, it's quite flexible, right? And it'll just probably require, like, a little bit of extension to the tool. It's entirely possible that you can…
David Krevitt: drop in CSVs into Claude and say, hey, use this instead of Ahrefs, and it can… it will probably figure that out and use it correctly. I just can't, you know, guarantee until you actually go and do that, because we obviously haven't tested, like, every edge case.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, and there's a couple questions also about why we're not using APIs from Ahrefs, or from local Falcon's MCP, or from…
Ryan Stewart: Windsor here, David?
Ryan Stewart: I mean, my opinion on it, guys, and David can probably provide more context, is that this is just much more accurate. It takes a little bit more time to set this up, but we find that there can be issues with pulling the Ahrefs data. We found quite a bit of, kind of, just hiccups in terms of the data pulled via API. That was just my experience. I don't know, David, if you.
David Krevitt: I think, yeah, the hiccups… I think the hiccups were, like, it eats a ton of credits, and every time. And, like, every… every time we were building something, you know, it would just… it would just eat up a lot of credits, and your account was often out of credits, so the CSVs were more reliable. It does,
David Krevitt: it, you know, it certainly can support the API if we want to do that. Loco Falcon API, or
David Krevitt: MCP, we could certainly support. These are the types of,
David Krevitt: Types of edge cases or feedback, like, once… once you guys get into this?
David Krevitt: We can definitely, like, extend the tool, to do this stuff, and…
Ryan Stewart: John.
David Krevitt: Yeah, yeah, there's gonna be a ton of these, like, little things that we wanna…
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, and from our point of view, too, I prefer stuff that works versus stuff that, like, is just continuously breaking. Especially, too, when you're working on your own, right? Without us here, like, 12 p.m. at night, right? It can be frustrating. So, for me, a little bit more work on the front end is much more preferable.
Ryan Stewart: But you can also see here, too, that, like, it will… I… so this is after I gave it all the stuff, I told it all the stuff from the folders, it will come back and tell you if there's a mismatch, if there's other stuff needed, tool screenshots, etc.
Ryan Stewart: And then, once it has that, now it will summarize all the data that it has, right? So it goes through all its checkpoints, this is a good place for you to look at stuff, and if something doesn't look right, you can tell it before it builds the proposal, because once it starts building a proposal, it's going to eat more credits, also takes…
Ryan Stewart: takes a good 10-15 minutes to build a proposal, because it's a pretty massive file. So, again, here's kind of checkpoint one for you to check the data, to make sure that everything looks solid. This built a little traffic declining thing, so we can look here, and again, just…
Ryan Stewart: Make sure everything looks good.
Ryan Stewart: the different summaries of the three or four markets. We didn't have anything on Sumter, I didn't find it, so that's on the client, not on us.
Ryan Stewart: Bleeding pages, growing pages, quick win keyword opportunities. I mean, this in itself is pretty cool, but we're obviously gonna push this into,
Ryan Stewart: into a file here. We now continue. So now, this is where it starts to pull in the angle options, right? And this is one of my favorite parts about this.
Ryan Stewart: it goes through and it analyzes the data sets for you. So, keyword collapse, number one. That's always the easiest one, guys, whenever we're selling SEO, and it's a lack of traffic falling or keywords, it'll find…
Ryan Stewart: you know, key… key keywords that are falling, right? So, like, big bottom funnel keywords that they've lost over time. It will do a lot of this kind of, like, basically a traffic loss analysis for you, which is super impactful, because, quite frankly, like, most of the leads that you're gonna get are probably working off of
Ryan Stewart: loss in traffic, you know, or just lack of performance in general. That's why they're looking or soliciting an agency. Another one that I pulled up is a strong competitor.
Ryan Stewart: Our attorneys love hearing about competitors and what they're doing.
Ryan Stewart: So this is a single name diversity, not a market, that's a sharper pitch than competitive landscape, so that's another element that I came up with. And then a third one here, local SEO is working, but the site SEO is broken, right? So, that's what I was saying, that they're ranking first for one of their Maps Pack locations, but they're… they're just bleeding traffic off the website.
Ryan Stewart: So then it just kind of cleans these up into a little bit more options for what to go with here. I usually tell it, and these are just the same ones that I just showed you, to go with kind of all three of them, because I think it's all three kind of good information.
Ryan Stewart: Then it builds a slide-by-slide outline for you for just to kind of give it final approval, and then we have it now run. So I'm now going to show you the proposal here that it came up with.
Ryan Stewart: And then I'm gonna show you side-by-side with, with what?
Ryan Stewart: the Weber's proposal for this look like. This is actually a real client that we're pitching. So this is the title slide, just pulls through the client's information,
Ryan Stewart: Now it gets into the executive summary, so this is some of the angles that we are talking about here, right? So, pulling through metrics, some of the key challenges here. And it's just important, too, guys, like, these proposals
Ryan Stewart: you want to make sure that you're reviewing it on a call with them. These should not be sent to the prospect. I mean, sometimes they're going to insist, and if they insist, then they're probably not going to close this anyways. Y'all, like, you want to make sure that you have a call here booked to review this with them.
Ryan Stewart: because you want to really drill into these kind of, like, talking points here. These are the talking points that you're really going to want to hit. Some opportunities that I came up with, and y'all are going to have access to this exact file, too, so you can review it. It'll be up in school by the end of this proposal. You can go through as I just kind of jump through slides here.
Ryan Stewart: So, competitive landscape here, this is the prospect here, and then it's just pulling through the other 3 competitors here.
Ryan Stewart: I'm gonna show you kind of how we designed these two in ours as well. Now we're getting into website performance. I love this slide here. So this is pulling through Ahrefs keyword data historically, domain rating, it's pulling through a, you know, the loss of the traffic here, just kind of showing the traffic value and traffic going down.
Ryan Stewart: This is a really good slide, too, because now this is why I think this is important. You know, I get asked all the time, because prospects… again, this is just Ahrefs today, y'all, like, this is… anyone who has access to the tool can pull this. But what I really like about what we built here is it pulls through why, so it pulls through some great suggestions here.
Ryan Stewart: So, core update happened, a couple updates here, and then, some location pages that actually fell off the map. So again, more like…
Ryan Stewart: informational… not just informational, but I think, like, good information, like, quality information for the prospect on why, like, what's… okay, great, I'm losing traffic, but, like, why? What's going on? These are just, again, an opportunity to showcase your expertise.
Ryan Stewart: this is all done for you. Like, you don't have to spend time combing through this anymore. I remember what… a year or two years ago, I used to have to go to Caesar and be like, hey man, we got this prospect, they're losing a lot of traffic, can you audit it and tell me why? And it would take them, like, 4 hours to come up with stuff like this, you know?
Ryan Stewart: Now it's just… it's all done for us. So this is a… this is an impactful slide, too. This is looking at… this is segmenting their traffic…
Ryan Stewart: The organic traffic by…
Ryan Stewart: funnel stage, right? So, top, mid funnel, and then bottom funnel here, and it's pulling through some of the keywords that it's ranking for, and then also kind of like a share of voice within the website. So, I use this quite a bit. I use kind of a corny analogy on these calls.
Ryan Stewart: Where I tell that a lot of these prospects have what's called, like, a barbell website, meaning instead of, like, a funnel, like an actual, kind of, like, stacked funnel, they have a barbell where it's big on the top, skinny in the middle, and then big on the bottom, right? It's a barbell. It's kind of like what's happening with the United States right now, right? Like.
Ryan Stewart: barbell in terms of, like, the distribution of wealth, right? Very, like, evaporating middle class within a very large… not a very large, but, like, a high concentration of wealth at the top, and a lot of people who are losing stuff, right? And I kind of use that corny analogy that, like.
Ryan Stewart: your website kind of looks like our economy right now, right? Anyways,
Ryan Stewart: evaporating middle class, right? Because this is really where we want to see most of the keywords here, is going to be here in the middle. These are going to be those mid-funnel, keywords that actually drive business value and business impact here.
Ryan Stewart: Versus… so these are actually wrong. I would actually go back and re-prompt this. These keywords here. So this is… this is why… that's why we look at this stuff, because these are not top funnel keywords. These are decision keywords.
Ryan Stewart: I see what happened. The awareness stuff should be on top, the decision. So, again, this is why I go through this stuff.
Ryan Stewart: the awareness should be on top, so I would actually go back and reprompt this, and I would say, inside of Clot, and I can actually show you that, too. But I would go back through and re-prompt it and say, the awareness should be on top, should go awareness, decision, consideration, and then branded, should be the proper stage funnel, right? So just an example of…
Ryan Stewart: Of how we'd want to reprompt this stuff. But either way, right, it's an impactful slide that shows them kind of, like, the breakdown of traffic, where things are going.
Ryan Stewart: It's always a good talking point for us to really start drilling into now, like, some of these angles and opportunities for pitching. Now, we can kind of open it up, and when I see a lot of traffic at the top of the funnel, I usually will tell prospects about… I'll start to kind of, like, seed that angle of, like, hey.
Ryan Stewart: A lot of agencies are gonna pitch you, like, a ton of blog content. We focus on your bottom funnel pages, because that's gonna be what's driving phone calls, right? So I'm trying to look at this data and tie it back
Ryan Stewart: through angles to what they were telling me. They're like, yeah, like, we're not getting a lot of phone calls. Well, here's one of the reasons why, right? Like, you have a ton of traffic at the top of the funnel. Instead of building blog content, we need to go back and revisit your practice area pages, like your bottom funnel pages, right?
Ryan Stewart: So these are gonna be AI search citations. I just didn't give the screenshots. All you have to do is just take a screenshot of, Google AI overviews, ChatGPT, and just kind of show them where they are, and I'll show you in a second our web risk proposal, how that looks. All you have to do is just add these screenshots to the folders, and it will pull through. Very simple.
Ryan Stewart: Again, here's another screenshot here, too. I didn't put it in, but just a ChatGPT screenshot. You just go to ChatGPT, take this, and then put it in here. And it will then tell the prospect, basically, like, hey, like, you're not ranking inside of ChatGPT. And this is a very crude way of doing this. It's not like… because the way ChatGPT works is really you want to be tracking the referral traffic from Google Analytics.
Ryan Stewart: But…
Ryan Stewart: this just kind of gives them a visual of, like, hey, you're not really performing. And again, I'm going to show you ours in a second. So now we move into local performance here. So this is pulling… these are great slides, man. Especially for multi-location businesses, even single-location businesses, right? Where, like, it's pulling through.
Ryan Stewart: Their current rankings, their share of voice, all this data is being pulled from Local Falcon, that's where it's getting this data from. Average rank, Google reviews, and then top 3 competitors over here as well, and a little bit of analysis.
Ryan Stewart: And then again, so, like, this is a 4-location business, 3-location business.
Ryan Stewart: It's great, this is all green here, but we tell them now, again, areas of opportunity, angles, hey.
Ryan Stewart: you're dominating here. I guarantee you're probably getting 50 to 70 phone calls a month from this listing alone. These are underperforming. Your share of voice in these markets, it's not doing well, especially here. We really need to pick these up. Here's how we can do that. Review generation.
Ryan Stewart: local content, local links, etc, right? Now this is going through and just pulling through competitors by office location to show them what they're up against from, like, a review point of view, and just kind of, like, overall market leaders in those. Now we get into practice areas. So again, we work with lawyers, so this is called practice areas.
Ryan Stewart: If you're doing e-commerce, this could be, like, product pages. If you're doing,
Ryan Stewart: home services, it could be service pages, right? Like, these are just gonna be the bottom funnel, high intent pages on the website that are gonna draw in
Ryan Stewart: high intent traffic, that are tied to keywords that are actually gonna drive, you know, phone calls. So, this pulls through the total number of pages, the pages with traffic, pages with zero traffic. So, again, like, what I'm looking for here is to tell that story and build that narrative of.
Ryan Stewart: yeah, you're not getting phone calls because your key pages aren't ranking, right? Like, these are the pages that matter, this is what we focus on.
Ryan Stewart: They're there, but, like, they're completely underperforming.
Ryan Stewart: So this goes into citations. I actually cut this out quite a bit. I don't find this to be the most impactful talking point slide, but it's in here either way. It just pulls through, and it will say, like, if they're missing key citations, like BBB, Yelp, etc. I usually cut this one out because
Ryan Stewart: to be honest with you, like, it doesn't really land too well with prospects. Sometimes they'll be like, oh, we're on Yelp, and I'm like, no, you're not. It's just… it's just kind of… not a high-impact slide. So, again, we're throwing a lot of stuff in here for you to customize and choose this.
Ryan Stewart: My personal preference is I cut this out. And I'm always looking for a way to cut this stuff down, too. I don't think you want to have, like, a massive, massive, massive proposal. I'm always looking to kind of prune these things. Now this goes into top 10 organic pages.
Ryan Stewart: So again, I like to show them, if I'm pitching this, I say, look at your top 5 pages here, right? Your first one, getting the most traffic, is your homepage, and it's because it's branded, right? It's not a bad thing, it's great that
Ryan Stewart: you have branded search, but, like, those aren't keywords that are really driving new business, those are people that are… we're not gonna hire you. Your next 3 pages, top… rounding out the top 4 pages on your website, are all, like.
Ryan Stewart: high-level in… like, this is… is Columbia, South Carolina safe? Is that a bad keyword for a criminal offense, Tony? It's not a bad keyword, but, like, you don't want that as your number two page, number two keyword on the website, because it's not driving phone calls. That's somebody who's probably looking to relocate to the area, right? So I understand why they would have this page.
Ryan Stewart: But it's not driving any phone calls for them, right? Same thing here, what is a criminal defense?
Ryan Stewart: I mean, they're a criminal defense firm. Is it a bad page to have? No, it's not. But, like, from a overall value point of view.
Ryan Stewart: searches like this are, first of all, getting gobbled up by AI overviews, and second of all, it's just not really going to drive business value for the firm.
Ryan Stewart: So then, I guess just more here on practice area pages, breaking down kind of, like, practice areas, total pages, with traffic, resources, blog content, just showing them kind of a segmentation of how this is working.
Ryan Stewart: all the search opportunity that's available to them, and where it's going. So, these are the keywords that we want to target. You're not ranking very well for them. Can you guys feel how this is, like.
Ryan Stewart: Building value and kind of, like, understanding and context, and building a pitch for me, too, to then come in and be like, we just showed you all this
Ryan Stewart: awesome information here.
Ryan Stewart: here's some competitor stuff, and again, like, I actually… I cut a lot of this stuff out. I'm gonna show you our proposal in just one second, I promise. But I'm just kind of showing this. I actually cut this out, too, so this is, well, this is the backlinks, I keep this in. Backlinks is an important talking point for us, because we do sell links,
Ryan Stewart: So this just goes through and it shows the prospect versus 3 competitors, and just kind of shows referring domains, follow links, you know, just kind of like a nice visual slide here to, again, start to talk about link deficiency.
Ryan Stewart: And it opens up an opportunity for me to then pitch links, right? So the technical stuff, unless there's, like, glaring errors here, again, I usually cut this one out. This is pulling from…
Ryan Stewart: Screaming Frog. Again, I just find that this slide, they start to glaze over a little bit, especially at this point in the presentation. They're just like.
Ryan Stewart: Okay.
Ryan Stewart: Next. So, I'm always looking for slides to cut out that don't really land,
Ryan Stewart: And again, this just kind of, like, summarizes, overall. Now we get into the plan of attack. So now, right, that was the analysis, right? Where that was, like I said, just about 80% of the slides in this is all about them, them, them, them, them. You, you, you, you, you. Now.
Ryan Stewart: here's how we can help, right? So, this is a trajectory that we have here, just a traffic projection analysis saying the red is your current… oops, that's cool. Your current trajectory, right? By doing nothing, you're gonna keep losing. By us, this is what we can expect. We're just giving it very high-level numbers. You can reprompt this however you want, if you're like.
Ryan Stewart: like, the numbers don't matter too much here, guys. Don't get too much caught up on, like, hey, what exactly should I be…
Ryan Stewart: Putting in as a…
Ryan Stewart: projection, we usually like to say a client will get, I don't know, 100% more traffic over 12 months, so… or 50% more traffic over 12 months. You can just kind of look at the stuff over time, look at their current performance, and just kind of show this to them.
Ryan Stewart: We also add in leads in ours, I'll show you that in just one second, just so they can send a little bit more. Now it just kind of gets into, like, a 6-month roadmap here, everything that is…
Ryan Stewart: you know, attacked and included, and just, like, what I love about this, too, is just, like, the level of specificity. This isn't, like, a high-level kind of, like, we're gonna do content, like, it's actually building out a roadmap that you can then take and use as a… as a project plan as well.
Ryan Stewart: And then there's pricing right here, so pricing slide, and then the rest are just case studies here. So, I'm gonna show you now our slides here, how we customize this, and then also the team, and then schedule another strategy call. So, this is this. All you guys have access to this. Now I'm gonna show you…
Ryan Stewart: the Weber's version of this. So we're actually pitching their injury firm, too, so it's a little bit different. If you see different data, it's not because it's hiccuping, it's just…
Ryan Stewart: This one is for their criminal defense practice, this one is for their personal practice. So already, right, what do you notice? Different branding. So…
Ryan Stewart: this is our Weber Spring Guidelines, built completely inside of Claude. I don't love it, like, I don't have it as our web font format, but this is, like, our Claude documentation. Anytime we're building a proposal for a document for a client.
Ryan Stewart: this is fed to it, the HTML file version of this, so Claude knows exactly what our fonts, our colors, stuff like that, just to keep consistency across.
Ryan Stewart: And also, too, like, tables, like, all this different stuff here.
Ryan Stewart: How did I build this? I just asked it to, and I went through, I spent a couple hours just kind of, like, reprompting, you can just kind of give it your current website, and then…
Ryan Stewart: you know, just kind of re-prompt it to get it to something that you want. I think this is important because, again, I look at, like, this is, like, a Claude… this is Claude font, right? I look at this and, like, this is Claude's default font.
Ryan Stewart: it's fine, I don't think there's anything wrong with it, but I just think as time goes on, and more people are doing this… is Sean in here? Sean's inside of Inner Circle, you know, and I…
Ryan Stewart: I tell Sean, you know, this stuff, that, like.
Ryan Stewart: he's been using Claude to build some really cool proposals and documentation, but I look at it, and I'm like, this is Claude all the way, you know? And again, I just think that, like, AI design is something that people are spotting and kind of ignoring, right? So we want to try and customize this to meet
Ryan Stewart: even if it's just fonts and colors, very simple stuff, because the rest of this, as you see, like, doesn't scream AI. It just… because of it, right? So, again.
Ryan Stewart: the slides are gonna look a little bit different than what you have, but it's the exact same data, it's the exact same information, it's just reformatted, and you can re-prompt this, right? So, again, run it for a prospect.
Ryan Stewart: Add in your brand guidelines, and spend a day, half a day, a couple hours, an evening, whatever, have a glass of wine, whatever it is that you do, and just kind of just go through and reprompt and reprompt and reprompt to get it customized, to what you're looking for.
Ryan Stewart: So again, this is our market comparison, same thing here, right? It's literally the same thing, it's just formatted and looks differently, right? I'm also going to provide you guys an example of our proposals.
Ryan Stewart: you already have the foundation of it, you know, I obviously ask so you don't, like.
Ryan Stewart: you can't… you can steal whatever, I don't really care, I guess, but, like, you know, just… this is… this is for context, for, like, what you can be working to redesign this to look like, to just clean things up a little bit, because we did impurposely make this, like, very generic-looking, because we're passing this to hundreds of people.
Ryan Stewart: So we wanted something that we're basically telling you guys, like, hey, customize this, because… so you're not sending the same proposals as other people are, right? And customize not just on a brand level, but also on a
Ryan Stewart: performance and input level, and I'll show you some small tweaks that I've done to ours versus this. So here's our organic performance.
Ryan Stewart: Here's a valuable prompt, right? So, like, this one here, they're losing traffic.
Ryan Stewart: what I like to do is I like to go in here and I say, okay, on slide, Performance 01, I'll reprompt it, and I'll say, they're losing traffic. Can you go and highlight their max point, and then from the rest of the part, either put a downward trend line, or put it in red, so they can clearly see that they're losing traffic. Like, I want this thing to scream, you are losing traffic, and you gotta do something about it.
Ryan Stewart: Very small, simple prompt that you can do. Again, exact same data, exact same chart. Again, it looks a little bit different because you start branding stuff, but all the data's the same here.
Ryan Stewart: So now is the why portion, right? So, algorithm, AI view, cannibalization.
Ryan Stewart: Same thing here, just, again, formatted to look a little bit different.
Ryan Stewart: So here's our, you can see here that I have these… this is, like, a… probably the proper way that it should be. Again, just something to keep in mind when you're prompting this, awareness should be on top.
Ryan Stewart: I had to pull through, like, an example keyword, and just kind of, like, a little bit of information, top keywords, and then a little bit clearer on the share of voice here, so they can see, you know, where their traffic is going.
Ryan Stewart: Here's the GEO comparison. So again, this one didn't pull through because I didn't put the screenshots in, but this is just pulling from Ahrefs. This is just Ahrefs data here. Again, just… I'm finding this…
Ryan Stewart: a very important talking point. Like, if I were you guys, I would be spending a lot of your time and effort thinking about the GEO portion of this, because this is something that I'm finding people are very interested in. So this is just showing two competitors versus them.
Ryan Stewart: AI overviews, I'll always tell this, too. I'll be like, hey, look, like, you're getting a lot of AI overviews here. That's not necessarily a good thing. I mean, it's not a bad thing, but, like.
Ryan Stewart: it's not helping you. We really want to be showing up at ChatGPT, and you got nothing here. And these are, again, just, like, angles, angles, angles that I'm pushing, to really sell ourselves and our services. So this is what I was talking about with the screenshots here, right? So, like, I didn't put the screenshot in here.
Ryan Stewart: But you can just kind of see now how, when you add in these screenshots, it gives a little bit of a visual break from just, like, tables and, like, charts, right? That was something that me and hernette worked on a lot, was we went through it, we were like, yo, like, we gotta figure out a way…
Ryan Stewart: to make this look a little bit less cloudy, in a sense. And adding screenshots is a great way to do that. It's super easy to do. You literally just take a screenshot.
Ryan Stewart: and just upload it directly, right? Like, just like you see our presentation decks, it's the same thing. I have this kind of format where I like to put, like, a screenshot for visual, just… especially when we're talking to attorneys or home services people, whatever, like.
Ryan Stewart: if you just send them, like, a lot of text like this, they're just gonna glaze over, right? So I'll really stop on the ones that have this, like, this is very…
Ryan Stewart: This is very…
Ryan Stewart: visual and very simple for them to see? We're not ranking. Paul, it's coming just from the Ahrefs overview, so, like…
Ryan Stewart: when you… when you put somebody in here, right, it's just coming from here.
Ryan Stewart: I don't have… I don't have the paid thing, it's way too expensive, it's crazy, but it's just pulling from this, so we just feed it a screenshot of this, and then it uses that to populate this here. So you gotta get the competitor stuff, too.
Ryan Stewart: So now you see our local pack stuff here, right? Very similar to what we had before, just formatted a little bit differently, because they have a lot of locations here. 2, 4, 6, 8… 8 locations, right? So we just have them formatted side-by-side here. Again, very simple prompt, looking at it and being like, okay.
Ryan Stewart: they have 10 locations, we don't want to add 10 slides to this. We can truncate that to 5 slides by just putting them side by side, right? Very simple visual prompt.
Ryan Stewart: GBP competitor audit, again, this is all the same stuff that's in here. As you can see, competitors by office.
Ryan Stewart: Ours just looks a little bit more Weber-y, right?
Ryan Stewart: And this one's also long because they do have 8 locations, right? So, mind you, it's a good-sized firm, paged by organic traffic, and again, all this is… it just looks different because…
Ryan Stewart: of our…
Ryan Stewart: brand guidelines that we fed in, right? And again, also me kind of going through and adding in screenshots of the practice area pages on here, all that stuff here as well.
Ryan Stewart: Backlink profile, we went through this already, same thing. Competitors, market average, and then also,
Ryan Stewart: Citations, again, I usually take this one out.
Ryan Stewart: Tech Collada usually take that as well. Now, plan of attack, again, same thing, 3 to 6, month roadmap. Organic track projection.
Ryan Stewart: She didn't put the leads in here. Sometimes we'll just add in a, 2% conversion rate to add in leads as well.
Ryan Stewart: But she didn't put that in here again, but it's the exact same slide here. So the pricing and timeline, I did change this to have it on a 6-month basis. You're free to re-prompt, take a screenshot of this, and add it into yours. I just think it's a little bit, a little bit cleaner to show, like, what they're getting and when. Very simple stuff.
Ryan Stewart: And then I'll just re-prompt when I'm going through this, like, hey, we're gonna do 10 links, we're gonna do 10,000 words, and then changing the cost on these things as well.
Ryan Stewart: And then these are just our screenshots for results here. So, I just take screenshots from Ahrefs, I put this little graphic on using Figma.
Ryan Stewart: And it just goes through, and it just walks through.
Ryan Stewart: you know.
Ryan Stewart: screenshot data of this. Logos here, again, very simple prompt that you can put in to add logos in. I actually don't have this slide inside of ours, I'm gonna take this one out, and that's it. That's the whole proposal. So, David, let's go ahead and start getting into some questions here now.
Ryan Stewart: So you guys can start bombing away with questions. Again, all this is available to you inside of school already. We're gonna update with the two versions of the proposals. I'll put our brain guidelines in here so you can see as well, and
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, let's go through the questions. I'm gonna scroll back up here, see if I missed anything. I was trying to get through a lot of them as I was going through. Elena already put the existing templates in here.
Ryan Stewart: Alright. Alright, alright, alright.
Ryan Stewart: So I answered the question about the MCPs for other…
Ryan Stewart: Answered that. Okay, so David said, for speaking with a marketing manager, it looks great for speaking with a marketing manager, but is there a version for someone who's just an owner? It's a great question, David, and that's kind of what I was talking about, too, about just going through,
Ryan Stewart: From our point of view, guys, like.
Ryan Stewart: it's so hard to customize these at your level. We have to try and come up with, like, a baseline foundation, and then try and impart the thinking on you to go through and do something like this, David. So, for what you can do with this, David, is go through and just cut down as much as possible. Like, cut out…
Ryan Stewart: the citation stuff, I would just focus on more visuals, so I would say, what are the slides that we have in here that have, like, very clean, easy-to-understand visuals? Charts.
Ryan Stewart: tables and screenshots, right? You can probably cut this thing in half easily by just doing that. You can remove the stuff on citations. You can probably remove the stuff on backlinks, too, the technical stuff for sure, right? Just focus on things that are, like.
Ryan Stewart: You're losing traffic.
Ryan Stewart: these are what your competitors… happening with your competitors, this is what's happening with your local rankings. I would focus on those, David.
Ryan Stewart: And it's also about how you present it to them. That's why it's really important that you do this over a call. We want to make sure that we're doing this over a call and not sending this to them, because even a marketing manager, Dave, we send this to them, they can get lost in this pretty easily, right? There's 28 slides in here of information.
Ryan Stewart: So it's a great question, and that's also, like, in the value of the prompting and reprompting, as well, to go through and just make sure that you're really customizing it to meet the needs of your prospect.
Ryan Stewart: Mike said, this proposal is the one we are going to create a potential client when they first schedule a meeting, so this will be done up front, presented during the first call? No, Mike, great question. So…
Ryan Stewart: The proposal… the sales process that we have, you can see it inside of school if you haven't been through it yet. First, a discovery call. The discovery call is a 30-minute call with the prospect. We have a list of discovery questions that's asking them about current marketing.
Ryan Stewart: What's working, what's not working, what they've done in the past, what are their expectations from marketing, what type of relationship are they looking for?
Ryan Stewart: That's the discovery process. Do not ever build this proposal, Mike, without going through that first. We have prospects sometimes that are like, hey, great, can you send me a proposal? I'm like, not without talking to me first.
Ryan Stewart: Because I need to qualify you as well, because this is quite a bit of work. Even though this is sped up, this is taking 2 hours now instead of 8, it's still 2 hours of time, that I don't want to have my team spend if they are not highly qualified. So the discovery call is to qualify them on your end to get information
Ryan Stewart: But to also build a rapport, like…
Ryan Stewart: people that are just like, yeah, send me a proposal, they're not serious. They're just not. People are, like, the people that are serious are gonna wanna talk to you, and know who they're hiring.
Ryan Stewart: before asking for a proposal. I would anyways do that.
David Krevitt: That's true across every…
Ryan Stewart: Yeah.
David Krevitt: ticket sales.
Ryan Stewart: So, this should be done. This is the analysis portion, Mike, this is part two.
Ryan Stewart: The discovery call, you have the discovery call. On the discovery call, book the analysis call with them. Say, hey, how's your… if you have the call on Monday, the discovery call, say, how's your Thursday looking? 10 a.m, let's get it booked, I just sent you an invite. Get that booked. Then show up to the analysis call with this analysis and proposal.
Ryan Stewart: That's the proper process, Mike.
Ryan Stewart: Jeff said, in your example, it has 3 locations. If it's a 6-location business, or 20-location business, do we need to prompt Claude with that info? Will the design adapt them automatically? Yeah, you're gonna need to feed it, if it has 20 locations, you're going to want to feed it all of the locations from local Falcon. It will automatically adapt
Ryan Stewart: the design, it will just add the necessary slides. And it will also know it, too, when you tell it in,
Ryan Stewart: You know, about the locations.
Ryan Stewart: Make sure you're charging accordingly, Jeff, for 20.
Ryan Stewart: Cliff said, structure is really compelling. What comes to mind for me is if you land the client, this is a great launch pad to start implementation inside of Cloud. Exactly. Like, what you guys are gonna see, our goal is to build a proposal for you guys that then feeds into the project plan.
Ryan Stewart: Right? Like, why… like, if it's doing the analysis here, and it kind of knows what we want to do, we should be able to build a pretty structured project plan automatically, right? That feeds directly into onboarding, and project kickoff. So that's… that's the…
Ryan Stewart: really the next step in this process, after we get through this, is going to start talking about doing the work using Claude, and using the analysis that Claude already did.
Ryan Stewart: Ryan, this is inside of the sales module in school.
Ryan Stewart: the sales module inside of school, yeah. Oh, Elena already asked that.
Ryan Stewart: Pierre said, this is a very heavy SEO proposal. Would you do the same proposal if a client is only interested in Google Ads, just because I'd sign a client with the intention of expanding services later? So, no, SEO is going to be, by far and away, the heaviest analysis portion. We have a Facebook ads proposal.
Ryan Stewart: That is a straight template, dude. Our Facebook ads proposal, I'm just like, here's the lawyer.
Ryan Stewart: this is what the expected cost per case is, this is what I'm charging, build me the proposal, and there's no analysis needed. The paid stuff is pretty straightforward, Pierre, because it's just like, what are they expecting to pay per client, right? If it is a home services company, what's the expected cost per lead? What's the expected cost per signed client?
Ryan Stewart: Right? So with Google Ads, I would… this would be a 5-8 page proposal saying, these are the keywords we're gonna target, this is the expected cost, this is the expected budget, this is the expected, projected, cost per side case. Let me actually just put my… give me a second here, I'll drop one of our Facebook ads proposals.
Ryan Stewart: I never send Google Ads proposals anymore, because it's kind of like, Google Ads is actually our upsell tack-on. I don't really lead with it,
Ryan Stewart: anymore, because there's not a lot of money for us, and it's very expensive for them.
Ryan Stewart: Sorry, let me just get a… So, but like…
Ryan Stewart: I'm gonna have to pull one.
Ryan Stewart: I'll make sure to drop it in a second, I don't have a…
Ryan Stewart: I don't have one pulling up offhand here.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, sorry. I'll get one, I'll get one for you guys soon.
Ryan Stewart: Jason said, do you do 12-month contracts month-to-month? We do month-to-month. I just tell them, like, you need to give us 6 months to see results, kind of a gentleman's agreement. It's a big selling point for them that we have the confidence, quote-unquote, to, like, not, make them sign a 12-month contract, so we do month-to-month for everything that we do.
Ryan Stewart: Joe said, this is probably a dumb question, there are no dumb questions here, y'all, trust me. I asked David a million dumb questions to build this, so I already asked them for you. But I'm new to the program, where should I go after the start here onboarding module? Like, what order should I follow? Just go through Joe exactly as it is, go from…
Ryan Stewart: Start here, to the AI Foundations, to sales, to SEO sprints, just literally, they're ordered for you in a process that you can just go through, module by module.
Ryan Stewart: Mike said, are we gonna get notifications when the connector is updated each time? Yes, you will. Elena will be announcing this stuff. It's why it's important to
Ryan Stewart: pay attention to announcements in here. I know it's, you know, overwhelming, but, Elena does a really good job of posting inside of school, sending emails, posting inside of Slack. We try and, you know, really over-communicate here and make sure that you guys have access to everything. So yeah, that will be announced every single time.
Ryan Stewart: Adam said, when it comes to getting Claude to use an existing template design, should we try and train Claude on our existing Google Drive templates, or is it tricky?
Ryan Stewart: So, I haven't had the best success With that,
Ryan Stewart: because we had a very specific… I had a lot of trouble trying to get our other proposal design into Claude. I don't know if you have something on that, David.
David Krevitt: Yeah, well, the one thing that the tools that setup will do is you can upload a deck, or just, like, if you have Drive connected to Claude, point it to a deck URL, and it will extract, like, your kind of palette… your color palette, basically what Ryan has for Weberis, right? Color palette, fonts, etc.
David Krevitt: And, it will set up, like, kind of presets for your… in your agency settings, and use those for…
David Krevitt: stuff like the proposal. But, yeah. But yeah, on top of that, like, if you wanted to add…
David Krevitt: new slides, you can… you can definitely do your best to, you know, point Claude to a specific deck and a specific slide and say, hey, I want to replicate this… this thing. And with a couple… if you… if you're patient with it, with a couple rounds of prompting, like, you should get to… to something reasonably close.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, I…
Ryan Stewart: I did this two months ago, maybe it's probably improved since then. Claude Design, I haven't played with it yet, but, like, you can build a pretty good design. I play with it a little bit, building a design system there. Here's what I would tell you. I would tell you that,
Ryan Stewart: just kind of like what I did, like, again.
Ryan Stewart: this doesn't match our website's branding. I don't really care, you know? Like, I don't… I just wanted something that's consistent, that's clean, that's simple. My suggestion would be to just use Claude to kind of build something new, and try and match your brand
Ryan Stewart: match it as close to your brand as possible. I had a lot of trouble trying to, like… I was very adamant, I was like, I love our Facebook ads proposal, I want to take this exact same thing in Google Slides and put it directly into Claude, and it…
Ryan Stewart: was the bane of my existence. Like, it just wouldn't do it. So I just kind of gave up on that, and I said, alright, let me just instead try and design a design system and brand guidelines that I could then refeed, and then kind of go and build slide by slide. I'm not gonna lie, like, the design part, guys, is… I'm very picky about design, too. So, for me.
Ryan Stewart: It was definitely the most complicated part about this, because Claude does such a good job with data, analysis.
Ryan Stewart: visualization presentation, but, like, the small formatting things on the branding element, it took me…
Ryan Stewart: it took us… it took me, like, a good 5 to 10 hours to really get this stuff kind of dialed in. But…
Ryan Stewart: You know, it's very doable, obviously.
David Krevitt: Adam, let's cover… let's cover Adam's question. Yeah, go for it. The client… having a client folder locally, and different members of your team, it's really important, and we've… Ryan and I have gotten through this, like, using some…
David Krevitt: some web sync method of syncing your local… a local folder, right? So that could be using the Google Drive desktop app, that could be using Dropbox, right? Any number of options there. You could use GitHub, although that's, like, a little stickier.
David Krevitt: But yeah, some method, whatever your chosen method is, to syncing your local folder to the cloud.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, David, you wanna… you just… I just saw your message on Slack, yeah, you're welcome to… Say that.
David Krevitt: Yeah, okay, cool, didn't want to jump the gun, but yeah, since a couple of you asked about local Falcon API, I just, while we're…
David Krevitt: While I was listening here, put together a version that uses the local Falcon API, so if anyone wants to test that, we'll get it uploaded and shared with you all. We don't personally use it.
David Krevitt: So we'll… we'll need your help going through it, but that's an example of, like, we're gonna want to iterate on this… on this stuff together.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah.
Ryan Stewart: And like I said, too, so Annette, is, was, first of all, aside from David, Annette was a huge help in helping push this stuff forward.
Ryan Stewart: But Annette is the one who builds our proposals, and she…
Ryan Stewart: the way that me and her work, and David would probably recommend a different workflow, right? But, like, me and her, she'll build it, the proposal, and then she'll send me the HTML file.
Ryan Stewart: And then I'll upload that to Claude and kind of do my own prompting to edit it. But we do… the issue with that is that we do lose the connection that David's talking about, which is really the proper way to do it. We're kind of working on getting that through GitHub. But it's also how, like.
Ryan Stewart: It's a workflow that works too, right? Like, once you have the H… once you have, like, a working HTML proposal, that thing is very valuable. Because you can use that as your foundation for proposals going forward.
Ryan Stewart: to what we do.
Ryan Stewart: Alright, so, Mike said, can you share your Cloud Cowork view so we can see how you're organizing things? Does each client need to be a project in Cloud Cowork?
Ryan Stewart: Also, should we just tell Claude to invoke the BPT agency OS?
Ryan Stewart: within a chat session, and that's how we start working with it. I'm trying to visualize how it's gonna be organized on the desktop app.
David Krevitt: Yeah, Ron, if you want to pull back up here, like, the example you went through… Yeah.
Ryan Stewart: Give me a second.
David Krevitt: The unsatisfying answer, Mike, is it's up to you.
David Krevitt: Like, you can have a separate folder, a separate project per client, you can have not-use projects at all,
David Krevitt: It's really what works for your team's, like, mental model.
David Krevitt: But yeah, if you, if you reference BPT, or anything about the agency OS, it will, it will pull up the, it will find the relevant, skills and tools to use.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so you can see, I literally just prompted it, Mike. I said, this is who I want to run a new proposal for, using the BPT proposal agent. I would also say, too, like, what I like to do, this is how I stay organized, this isn't about, like, the client stuff, I like to, like, whenever I'm doing anything web-ris-related proposals, I use the exact same kind of, like.
Ryan Stewart: co-work thread, if you will. I don't know if it's the right… the right thing for it, just to keep it all kind of, like, in one simple space. So, like, if I was gonna use this again to do another proposal, I would use this exact same…
Ryan Stewart: thread, that's one level of organization, but the client thing, so Claude did that for me, right? Like, the desktop folders that I was sharing with you guys here.
Ryan Stewart: Client folders.
Ryan Stewart: here, right? Like.
Ryan Stewart: Claude is ultimately… so client… also, too, like, we're talking about leads, not clients right now. Next week, when we start talking about deliverables, right, so, like, website quality audit, reporting.
Ryan Stewart: they'll be inside of the client's folder, right? Right now, it's a lead, so anytime we run a proposal.
Ryan Stewart: Claude actually creates this folder for me, right, David? So, like, it… I didn't, because I didn't create these folders.
David Krevitt: Yeah.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so…
David Krevitt: Create that, yeah.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, so Claude, as you're going through this, Mike, it's trained to set up these folder structures for you, and it does, like, I'm not gonna lie, like, it's helpful to have, just like I have here, it's helpful to have it open
Ryan Stewart: on your desktop as well, so you can look at it, too. So that way, Mike, because it does take some kind of, like.
Ryan Stewart: to connect your brain to this workflow as well, to see it and visualize it, I'm kind of the same way, to actually see it on your desktop. And you're also going to use it, like, you should be adding…
Ryan Stewart: the stuff.
Ryan Stewart: like, the images, the CSVs, directly here, so… you know, like.
Ryan Stewart: Again, all… everything that I just showed you was built
Ryan Stewart: by adding stuff inside of here, right? So, it's good to have an open mic, and it should help you to also kind of, like, visualize
Ryan Stewart: the folder structure as well, if that makes sense. Let me know if that makes sense.
Ryan Stewart: Pierre said, how does it automatically put everything into the correct client folder, or is that the data you upload? What's the trigger to create a folder for a client?
David Krevitt: Yeah, basically when it recognizes you're talking about a new client, or a new lead in the case of a proposal, it will ask, usually prompt you, and ask, like, do you want to create a new client, and ask you, Ryan, if you scroll down a little bit, I think it asks you for a little bit of context about this lead.
Ryan Stewart: Yeah.
David Krevitt: Who the contact was.
Ryan Stewart: Yep.
David Krevitt: A little bit further down…
Ryan Stewart: I actually asked this question, guys.
Ryan Stewart: How do I connect the folder? It just did it, automatically. It found the folder and it did it.
Ryan Stewart: Okay, cool. Yeah, and here's where I put in the information for it.
David Krevitt: So, it will recognize… it's, like, trying to recognize, oh, you're talking about a new client or new lead, and it will ask, do you want to create this lead or client?
Ryan Stewart: Yeah, and it pops up, like, it's a multiple-choice selection for you, you don't have to, like.
David Krevitt: Yeah.
Ryan Stewart: It just… it just does it for you. You know, like, and the best thing, too, honestly, is just… is just to do one. Even if you don't have a prospect, do, like, a proposal for your own website, just to get the… all this stuff, guys, just time on task. You know, it's just time on task to get it done.
Ryan Stewart: Alright, do we have any more questions before we wrap for the day?
Ryan Stewart: Alright, awesome. So, again.
Ryan Stewart: go through this stuff. We're here to help answer any questions that you have with it. We will be back very shortly, going through client deliverables. We're gonna start with the website quality audit,
Ryan Stewart: some real fun stuff that we're gonna start knocking out week after week here, y'all. So, as always, thanks, David, thanks, Elena, for everyone's hard work, and, we'll see you guys next week.
David Krevitt: Thanks, all. See ya.